http://www.icemiller.com/privacy-policy/

Last modified:  May 11, 2018
Ice Miller LLP (“we,” “us,” “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of your information. The following Privacy Policy sets forth our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of the information we receive through your use and navigation of www.icemiller.com (“website”). This Privacy Policy may occasionally change, so please refer to this page periodically to check for updates.
Scope
This Privacy Policy applies to our website and any subdomains of our website, unless explicitly stated otherwise, regardless of the medium in which it is accessed (e.g., via a web browser or mobile browser).
The Information We Collect From You
We may collect different types of information from you when you use or navigate our website:
Personal Information:  When you use and navigate the website, we may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, work or educational history, and other information that may be used to identify you or contact you (collectively, “Personal Information”) from you only when you provide such Personal Information to us voluntarily.
Website Usage Information: When you use and navigate our website, we may collect additional information from you that may not by itself reasonably identify you as the source (collectively, “Usage Information”). Usage Information may include, but is not limited to, information regarding your computer, your IP address, the type of Internet browser you are using, the location from which you are visiting the website, the type of computer operating system you are using to access the website, the domain name of the website from which you linked to the website, or the areas of the website you visited and the actions you performed on the website.
How We Collect Information
We may collect information about you from a variety of sources:
Directly From You. We collect Personal Information from you when you voluntarily provide such information to us by, for example, completing one of our various website forms to contact us, subscribe to receive email news alerts or information regarding our firm’s activities, registering to attend one of the firm’s events, and submitting a job application.
Through Your Use of the Website. Our systems may record your Usage Information as you use and navigate our website. For example, our servers automatically record Usage Information that your browser transmits when you visit our website. We also may automatically collect Usage Information about how you access and interact with the website through the use of automated tracking technology. We may use cookies, which are small data files that are transferred to a web browser, which enables our website to remember and customize your subsequent visit. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser to block the acceptance of cookies or to provide you with a warning prompt before you accept a cookie from the website. Please refer to your Internet browser’s instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, the functionality of the website may be limited, and you may not be able to participate in several of our website’s features. Additionally, we may use web beacons, which are single-pixel, electronic images embedded in the website that allow us to gather information about your browsing activities on the website. We may also use certain third-party applications, which may use cookies, to gather and analyze information about your browsing activities on the website.
How We Use Information
We may use information about you in the following ways:
Personal Information: We may use your Personal Information, which you voluntarily provide to us, for a variety of purposes, including to:
Directly contact you to respond to messages or inquiries that you submitted using our website forms;
Send you periodic updates about the firm’s insights and activities via email, in accordance with your subscription preferences and from which you may opt-out of receiving;
Process your job applications;
Analyze the effectiveness of our marketing activities; and
Manage our everyday business needs.
Usage Information: We may also use your Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including to:
Analyze website users’ browsing and usage activities and patterns to better understand users’ interests and preferences with respect to our services; and
Research the effectiveness of the website, which will help us to improve the website.
How We Disclose Information
We do not sell your information to third parties. We may, however, disclose your information to third parties in the following ways:
Third-Party Service Providers: We may share your Personal Information with third parties who assist us with our marketing efforts. We may also share your Usage Information, including cookies, with third-party applications and web analysis providers. For example, we share your Usage Information with Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google. Google Analytics plants a cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user each time you visit the Site, but the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. We use Google Analytics to analyze Usage Information and assist us in researching the effectiveness of our website and understanding website users’ preferences. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use, located at https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html, and Google’s Privacy Policy, located at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy. You may prevent Google Analytics from recognizing your future visits to the website by disabling cookies on your browser or installing Google Analytics’ opt-out browser add-on, which can be accessed at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Law Enforcement, Safety, and Legal Processes. We may share your Personal Information and/or Usage Information with law enforcement or other government officials if it relates to a criminal investigation or alleged criminal activity. We may also disclose your Personal Information and/or Usage Information if required or permitted to do so by law; for fraud protection and credit risk reduction purposes, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights or property of Ice Miller LLP or the users of the website; and to act under urgent circumstances to protect the safety of Ice Miller LLP, its employees, or a member of the public. We may also disclose your information to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, subpoena, or legal process.
Sale or Acquisition of Assets. If we become involved in a transaction involving the sale of our assets, such as a merger or acquisition, we may disclose and/or transfer your Personal Information as part of the transaction.
Security of Personal Information
We take reasonable measures to protect the information we collect from you. Unfortunately, no data transmitted over or accessible through the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we attempt to protect all Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant that Personal Information will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or from other nefarious or criminal activities, or in the event of a failure of computer hardware, software, or a telecommunications network. We will notify you in the event we become aware of a security breach involving your personally identifiable information (as defined by the applicable state and federal laws) stored by or for us. Ice Miller LLP cannot be responsible for disclosures of your Personal Information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties, and encourages you to exercise prudence in selecting the information you send via the Internet, including via email. Please do not send confidential or sensitive information to us through our website or via email until you speak with one of our attorneys and receive authorization to do so.
Individuals in the European Economic Area The European Union (EU) General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) provides individuals in the European Economic Area with the following rights:
To access the personal data we maintain about you
To receive information about how we process your personal data
To correct your personal data
To have your personal data erased
To object to or restrict how we process your personal data
To request your personal data be transferred to a third party
To withdraw any consent you may have given us to process your personal data
To exercise the above rights, please contact us at the information provided below. We will consider and process your request within a reasonable period of time. Please be aware under certain circumstances, the GDPR may limit your exercise of these rights.
Other Provisions
Accessing and Updating Personal Information and Opting-Out. If you would like to access, update, or modify your Personal Information or request us to delete your Personal Information, you may do so by contacting us at the contact information listed below. Further, if you would like to opt-out of receiving emails or other communications directly from us, you may do so by following any instructions included in the email or other communication or by contacting us at the contact information listed below. Opting-out from our communications or modifying, updating, or deleting your Personal Information will not result in the modification, updating, or deletion of any Personal Information that may reside in back-up or disaster-recovery storage.
Your California Privacy Rights. California law provides that California residents have a right to request businesses to tell them how their personal information has been shared with third parties, if at all, for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at the contact information listed below.
Do Not Track Signals. Certain web browsers and other devices you may use to access the website may permit you to indicate your preference that you do not wish to be “tracked” online. At this time, the website does not respond to "Do Not Track" signals.
Children Under 13. We do not market to and do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from or about a child under the age of 13 without the consent of the child’s parent or legal guardian. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected information from a child under 13 years of age, we will promptly take all reasonable measures to delete such information from our systems.
Links. Our website may contain links to third-party websites, including links that enable you to share the contents of our website through various social media platforms. If you click on one of those links, you will be taken to websites we do not control and to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. We are not responsible for such third-party websites, and encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and statements of those websites.
Updates to this Privacy Policy. We may periodically revise the Privacy Policy in our sole and absolute discretion to reflect changes in our business practices. If we revise the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the updated Privacy Policy on the website. Changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective and will apply to the information collected starting on the date we post the revised Privacy Policy on the website. Your continued use of our website after any change has become effective will constitute your acceptance of any change.
Contact Information
Please contact us at the contact information listed below:
© 2020 Ice Miller LLPThe Ice Miller logo is a registered trademark of Ice Miller LLP
© 2020 Ice Miller LLPThe Ice Miller logo is a registered trademark of Ice Miller LLP
View Full Site
View Mobile Optimized
